Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Central Region Freight Joint Area Committee Transcript Records 1954-2010 IBT0053
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2003, June 10 (Box 171, Folder 17)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2003, June 10 (Box 171, Folder 18)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 2003, June 10 (Box 171, Folder 19)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2003, June 10 (Box 171, Folder 20)
- Primary Dispatch Committee Meeting, 2003, June 10 (Box 172, Folder 1)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2003, June 10-11 (Box 172, Folder 2)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 2003, June 11 (Box 172, Folder 3)
- Drug Committee Meeting, 2003, September 9 (Box 172, Folder 4)
- Special Circumstances Committee Meeting, 2003, September 9 (Box 172, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2003, September 9 (Box 172, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2003, September 9 (Box 172, Folder 7)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2003, September 9 (Box 172, Folder 8)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2003, September 9 (Box 172, Folder 9)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2003, September 9-11 (Box 172, Folder 10)
- National Intermodal Committee Meeting, 2003, October 1 (Box 172, Folder 11)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2003, December 9 (Box 172, Folder 12)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2003, December 9 (Box 172, Folder 13)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2003, December 9 (Box 172, Folder 14)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2003, December 9 (Box 172, Folder 15)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2003, December 9 (Box 172, Folder 16)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2004, March 9 (Box 172, Folder 17)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2004, March 9 (Box 172, Folder 18)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2004, March 9 (Box 172, Folder 19)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2004, March 9 (Box 172, Folder 20)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2004, March 9-10 (Box 172, Folder 21)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2004, March 18 (Box 172, Folder 22)
- National Intermodal Committee Meeting, 2004, March 30 (Box 172, Folder 23)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2004, April 1 (Box 172, Folder 24)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2004, June 8 (Box 173, Folder 1)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 2004, June 8 (Box 173, Folder 2)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2004, June 8 (Box 173, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2004, June 8 (Box 173, Folder 4)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2004, June 8 (Box 173, Folder 5)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2004, June 8 (Box 173, Folder 6)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2004, June 8 (Box 173, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2004, June 8 (Box 173, Folder 8)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2004, June 8 (Box 173, Folder 9)
- National Intermodal Committee Meeting, 2004, July 13-14 (Box 173, Folder 10)
- Joint National Master Committee Meeting, 2004, August 12 (Box 173, Folder 11)
- Special Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2004, August 12 (Box 173, Folder 12)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2004, September 14 (Box 173, Folder 13)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 2004, September 14 (Box 173, Folder 14)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2004, September 14 (Box 173, Folder 15)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2004, September 14 (Box 173, Folder 16)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2004, September 14-15 (Box 173, Folder 17)
- Roadway Express Operations Manual, 2004, October 25 (Box 173, Folder 18)
- National Intermodal Committee Meeting, 2004, November 9-10 (Box 173, Folder 19)
- National Grievance Committee Meeting, 2004, November 10 (Box 173, Folder 20)
- National Master Negotiating Committee Meeting, 2004, November 10 (Box 173, Folder 21)
- Special Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2004, November 10 (Box 173, Folder 22)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2004, December 7 (Box 173, Folder 23)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 2004, December 7 (Box 173, Folder 24)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2004, December 7 (Box 173, Folder 25)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2004, December 7 (Box 173, Folder 26)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2004, December 7 (Box 173, Folder 27)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2004, December 7-8 (Box 173, Folder 28)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 2004, December 8 (Box 173, Folder 29)
- Special Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2004, December 16 (Box 173, Folder 30)
- Special Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2004, December 16 (Box 174, Folder 1)
- Special Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2004, December 16 (Box 174, Folder 2)
- Special Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2004, December 16 (Box 174, Folder 3)
- Special Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2004, December 16 (Box 174, Folder 4)
- National Intermodal Committee Meeting, 2005, January 11-12 (Box 174, Folder 5)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2005, March 7 (Box 174, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2005, March 7 (Box 174, Folder 7)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 2005, March 8 (Box 174, Folder 8)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2005, March 8 (Box 174, Folder 9)
- Central States Committee Meeting, 2005, March 8 (Box 174, Folder 10)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2005, March 8 (Box 174, Folder 11)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2005, March 8 (Box 174, Folder 12)
- Special Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2005, April 6 (Box 174, Folder 13)
- Special Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2005, April 7 (Box 174, Folder 14)
- Roadway Express Operations Manual, 2005, April 7 (Box 174, Folder 15)
- National Intermodal Committee Meeting, 2005, April 12 (Box 174, Folder 16)
- Special Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2005, May 17 (Box 174, Folder 17)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2005, June 14 (Box 174, Folder 18)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2005, June 14 (Box 174, Folder 19)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2005, June 14 (Box 174, Folder 20)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2005, June 14 (Box 174, Folder 21)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2005, June 14 (Box 174, Folder 22)
- National Intermodal Committee Meeting, 2005, July 13 (Box 175, Folder 1)
- Special Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2005, September 1 (Box 175, Folder 2)
- Special Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2005, September 1 & 13 (Box 175, Folder 3)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2005, September 13 (Box 175, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2005, September 13 (Box 175, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2005, September 13 (Box 175, Folder 6)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2005, September 13 (Box 175, Folder 7)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2005, September 13 (Box 175, Folder 8)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 2005, September 14 (Box 175, Folder 9)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2005, December 13 (Box 175, Folder 10)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2005, December 13 (Box 175, Folder 11)
- Special Circumstances Committee Meeting, 2005, December 13 (Box 175, Folder 12)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2005, December 13 (Box 175, Folder 13)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2005, December 13 (Box 175, Folder 14)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2005, December 13 (Box 175, Folder 15)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 2006, February 1 (Box 175, Folder 16)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 2006, February 1 (Box 175, Folder 17)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 2006, February 1 (Box 176, Folder 1)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 2006, March 14 (Box 176, Folder 2)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2006, March 14 (Box 176, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2006, March 14 (Box 176, Folder 4)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2006, March 14 (Box 176, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2006, March 14 (Box 176, Folder 6)
- National Intermodal Committee Meeting, 2006, April 19 (Box 176, Folder 7)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2006, April 24 (Box 176, Folder 8)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2006, May 23 (Box 176, Folder 9)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2006, May 23 (Box 176, Folder 10)
- Article VI Committee Meeting, 2006, May 23 (Box 176, Folder 11)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2006, May 23 (Box 176, Folder 12)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2006, May 23 (Box 176, Folder 13)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2006, May 23 (Box 176, Folder 14)
- National Intermodal Committee Meeting, 2006, July 12 (Box 176, Folder 15)
- Change of Operations Grievance Committee Meeting, 2006, July 12 (Box 176, Folder 16)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2006, September 20 (Box 176, Folder 17)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2006, September 20 (Box 176, Folder 18)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2006, September 20 (Box 176, Folder 19)
- Special Circumstances Committee Meeting, 2006, September 23 (Box 176, Folder 20)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2006, September 23 (Box 176, Folder 21)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2006, December 12 (Box 176, Folder 22)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2006, December 12 (Box 176, Folder 23)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2006, December 12 (Box 176, Folder 24)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2006, December 12 (Box 176, Folder 25)
- Article VI Committee Meeting, 2006, December 12 (Box 176, Folder 26)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2006, December 12 (Box 176, Folder 27)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2007, January 17 (Box 177, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Commitee Meeting [1 of 3], 2007, February 12 (Box 177, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 2007, February 12 (Box 177, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 2007, February 12 (Box 177, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2007, March 13 (Box 177, Folder 5)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2007, March 13 (Box 177, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2007, March 13 (Box 177, Folder 7)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2007, March 13 (Box 177, Folder 8)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2007, March 13-14 (Box 177, Folder 9)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2007, June 12 (Box 177, Folder 10)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2007, June 12 (Box 177, Folder 11)
- Special Circumstances Committee Meeting, 2007, June 12 (Box 177, Folder 12)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2007, June 12 (Box 177, Folder 13)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2007, June 12-13 (Box 177, Folder 14)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2007, July 24 (Box 177, Folder 15)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2007, August 30 (Box 178, Folder 1)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2007, September 11 (Box 178, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2007, September 11 (Box 178, Folder 3)
- Special Circumstances Committee Meeting, 2007, September 11 (Box 178, Folder 4)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2007, September 11 (Box 178, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2007, December 18 (Box 178, Folder 6)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2007, December 18 (Box 178, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2007, December 18 (Box 178, Folder 8)
- Durg and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2007, December 18 (Box 178, Folder 9)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2007, December 18 (Box 178, Folder 10)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2008, March 11 (Box 178, Folder 11)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2008, March 11 (Box 178, Folder 12)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2008, March 11 (Box 178, Folder 13)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2008, March 11 (Box 178, Folder 14)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2008, March 11-12 (Box 178, Folder 15)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2008, June 10 (Box 178, Folder 16)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2008, June 10 (Box 178, Folder 17)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2008, June 10 (Box 178, Folder 18)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2008, June 10 (Box 178, Folder 19)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2008, June 10 (Box 178, Folder 20)
- Article VI Committee Meeting, 2008, June 11 (Box 178, Folder 21)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2008, September 15 (Box 178, Folder 22)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2008, September 15-16 (Box 178, Folder 23)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2008, September 16 (Box 178, Folder 24)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2008, September 16 (Box 178, Folder 25)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2008, September 16 (Box 178, Folder 26)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 2008, September 16 (Box 178, Folder 27)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2008, September 16 (Box 178, Folder 28)
- Special Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2008, November 10 (Box 178, Folder 29)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2008, December 9 (Box 178, Folder 30)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2008, December 9 (Box 178, Folder 31)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2008, December 9 (Box 178, Folder 32)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2008, December 9 (Box 178, Folder 33)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2008, December 9 (Box 178, Folder 34)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2008, December 9 (Box 178, Folder 35)
- Special Circumstances Committee Meeting, 2008, December 9 (Box 178, Folder 36)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2009, March 10 (Box 179, Folder 1)
- Special Circumstances Committee Meeting, 2009, March 10 (Box 179, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2009, March 10 (Box 179, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2009, March 10 (Box 179, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2009, May 27 (Box 179, Folder 5)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2009, June 9 (Box 179, Folder 6)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2009, June 9 (Box 179, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2009, June 9 (Box 179, Folder 8)
- Special Circumstances Committee Meeting, 2009, June 9 (Box 179, Folder 9)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2009, June 9 (Box 179, Folder 10)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2009, June 9 (Box 179, Folder 11)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2009, September 15 (Box 179, Folder 12)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2009, September 15 (Box 179, Folder 13)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2009, September 15 (Box 179, Folder 14)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2009, September 15 (Box 179, Folder 15)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2009, September 15 (Box 179, Folder 16)
- Article VI Committee Meeting, 2009, September 15-16 (Box 179, Folder 17)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2009, December 8 (Box 179, Folder 18)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2009, December 8 (Box 179, Folder 19)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2009, December 8 (Box 179, Folder 20)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2009, December 8 (Box 179, Folder 21)
- Article VI Committee Meeting, 2009, December 9 (Box 180, Folder 1)
- Article VI Committee Meeting, 2010, March 9 (Box 180, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2010, March 9 (Box 180, Folder 3)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2010, March 9 (Box 180, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2010, June 15 (Box 180, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2010, June 15 (Box 180, Folder 6)
- Article VI Committee Meeting, 2010, June 15 (Box 180, Folder 7)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2010, June 15 (Box 180, Folder 8)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2010, June 15 (Box 180, Folder 9)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2010, September 14 (Box 180, Folder 10)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 2010, September 14 (Box 180, Folder 11)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2010, September 14 (Box 180, Folder 12)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2010, September 14 (Box 180, Folder 13)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2010, December 7 (Box 180, Folder 14)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2010, December 7 (Box 180, Folder 15)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2010, December 7 (Box 180, Folder 16)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2010, December 7 (Box 180, Folder 17)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2010, December 7 (Box 180, Folder 18)